•	Explanation of the design
Our design creates main classes for Nurse, Patient, Waiting_List, and abstract class Data. Urgency, Medical_History, Symptoms, and Vital_Signs are the subclasses of Data, while Waiting_Patient is a subclass of Patient. 
	-Nurse: The class Nurse aims to implements the responsibilities of a nurse, as described in the “Feature List” from the client request, we have also included a login feature so that there is a record of which nurse made the modifications to the data.
	-Patient: Patient is a class used to organize the data for a specific patient, including vital signs, symptoms, medical history and urgency. It also contains a subclass waiting_patient, which has a status marking feature for patients who have not been seen by a doctor.
	-Data (Abstract): The abstract class Data which implements the basic responsibilities of data that would be used in this system, such as record, save, add and update. 
	-Vital_Signs (Parent: Data): Vital_Signs is a subclass of Data, and it aims to record and save all the vital signs of a certain patient, also retains the history records.
	-Symptoms (Parent: Data): Symptoms is another subclass of Data, which focuses on taking in the descriptions of symptoms and maintains the previous records.
	-Medical_History (Parent: Data): The class records the medical history of the patient and keeps track of his or her previous medical history (which could be implemented by nurses, for checking and recording purporse.)
	-Urgency (Parent:Data): The class calculates urgency points and providing the worsening/improving status of this patient. 
	-Waiting_Patient (Parent: Patient): The class subclassed Patient, and gives a feature of marking a patient as "waiting". 
	-Waiting_List: The class is in charge of ordering waiting patients by either arrival time or urgency. 
•	Format of Files
-Nurse: Both username and password should be strings.
-Patient: Patient’s name, date of birth, and health card number will be saved as Strings. The arrival time will be saved as string with the format of "YYMMDD HH:MM"
-Vital_Signs: Temperature is saved in float number, while blood pressure (both systolic and diastolic) and heart rate are saved as integers. One set of these values represents the patient's vital signs at a particular time point (whereas the time is saved as a string as the one in Patient class), and the set of values is saved as a hashset, and the history data will be saved in a TreeMap with time as keys and sets of values as values of TreeMap.
-Symptoms: The text description and time will be saved as strings, and the hitory data will be saved in a TreeMap with time as the keys and descriptions as the values.
-Medical_History: Each descritpion will be saved as a string with the format "[Patient Name] has been seen by doctor at YYMMDD HH:MM", and the previous history will be saved as a Treeset of strings(descriptions) .
-Urgency: Urgency points will be integers, and the worsening/improving status will be saved as integers with values 0(stable),1(worsening) and -1(improving).
-Waiting_Patients: The status of a patient will be recorded using Boolean values, True for "waiting" and False for "seen".
-Waiting_List: The waiting patients list will be saved as a Arraylist ordered by arrival time, and the urgency list will be saved as a ArrayList ordered by decreasing urgency.
-Time will always be saved as string “YYYYMMDD HH:MM”
•	Justification and Data Structure
The design overall is quite satisfying as we were able to use object-oriented ideas, inheritance, and dealt with all requests. We implemented inheritance multiple times, and used an abstract class in order to make each data into smaller classes, thus clarifying the purpose of each class. For most of the values in the program, we decided to save them as strings, as there are names and date of birth. We decided to use ArrayList for Waiting_List as it is possible to order the patients, and it can return the position of a patient. For Waiting_Patients, we decided to use Boolean values, so that if a patient is waiting, the value would be True, otherwise False.